[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121008pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 36, "question": "What do you make of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 37, "answer": "Well, certainly the debate was a defining moment in this campaign, but I think it's pretty simple.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121008pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "Do you think the debate performance has actually carried over weight with women generally?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "I think, you know, two observations on that, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121008pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 56, "question": "I mean can you articulate for me exactly what the key difference would be, if he became president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "WP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 57, "answer": "A number of key differences.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Israel", "Iran"]}, "docId": "121008pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "RBR", "JJ", "CC", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJR", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 103, "question": "So presumably you would like to see -- would you like to see Mubarak?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", ":", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 104, "answer": "Israel is not more secure and Iran is closer to a nuclear weapon.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121008pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ":", "RB", ",", "VB", ":", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "VBZ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 108, "question": "I mean where would you go with this threat?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 109, "answer": "Well, what I would want -- well, let -- what I would want and what we didn't have and what we don't have is I'd like to have a strategy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Coleman"], "LOCATION": ["Syria"]}, "docId": "121008pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 143, "question": "What would you say to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 144, "answer": "I think the most interesting thing about Governor Romney is not just this speech but his entire foreign policy approach is the complete absence of specifics and we even heard that from former Senator Coleman there, so he's upset about the situation in Syria.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121008pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "It was a fairly dismal performance, wasn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "Correct.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121008pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 195, "question": "This is catastrophic, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 196, "answer": "Well, it's not catastrophic.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121008pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 229, "question": "What happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 230, "answer": "Well --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121008pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 233, "question": "Are you correcting your prediction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 234, "answer": "We are.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121008pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 250, "question": "If Romney can?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "MD", "."], "aSentId": 251, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121008pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 261, "question": "Would you agree with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 262, "answer": "Well, in the debate he was able to reposition himself toward the center of the electorate.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121008pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RBR", "."], "qSentId": 371, "question": "I mean you must be, I would imagine, jubilant at some of these poll numbers today but in reality, can they hold and what is going on with women voters here, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "NN", "CC", "IN", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "NNS", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 372, "answer": "So I don't think it's about personality as you said earlier.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121008pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 388, "question": "Because if he's not, isn't he just talking a lot of hot air?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 389, "answer": "I think it's less about the differences in what goals or ultimate vision the two men have, and it's a difference in how they would want to execute them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "121008pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "What does that mean?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "Look, I think Mitt Romney's foreign policy can be described like this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121008pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 467, "question": "Why do you want to talk out now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 468, "answer": "I feel that it's about time, the time that all this commotion was happening, we were forced to leave our home.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121008pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "What went through your mind in that moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "At that moment it feel like I couldn't believe what had happened.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121008pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 485, "question": "Have you -- have you come to terms with the possibility that George may go to prison for 25 or 30 years if he's found guilty?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CD", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 486, "answer": "I believe in the judicial system.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Morgan"]}, "docId": "121008pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "EX", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "MD", "VB", "RB", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "IN", "WP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 490, "question": "Do you -- as his mother, do you wish that George had never gone out carrying a gun that evening?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "RP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 491, "answer": "Mr. Morgan, there are so many things that we, you know, can wish as parents, but I will not answer to that question because I don't want, you know, people to elaborate of what, you know, the mother has said.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121008pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 492, "question": "If you had the chance, Gladys, to talk to Trayvon Martin's parents, what would you say to them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "TO", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 493, "answer": "It was already said by a statement that my son had made public.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gladys", "Trayvon Martin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121008pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 495, "question": "What would you say as a mother to another mother who had lost her son?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 496, "answer": "That I'm deeply sorry for what had happened.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121008pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 502, "question": "How is George doing now, how is he coping with incarceration, how is he coping with the impending trial?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "NNP", "VBG", "RB", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 503, "answer": "Well, he's not incarcerated right now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121008pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "I mean how free is he to go about?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "That's right, that's exactly right, it is restrictive.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Morgan"]}, "docId": "121008pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "If the situation had been reversed, if it had been George who was going back to visit a family relative, having gone to a store who was unarmed, and he got into an altercation with somebody, Trayvon Martin, for argument's sake, and Trayvon Martin had produced a gun and shot your son dead, do you think you would feel differently about what happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "NNP", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "JJ", ",", "VBG", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "POS", "NN", ",", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "Mr. Morgan, I don't want to touch anything that has to do directly with the case.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Trayvon Martin"], "PERSON": ["George", "Trayvon Martin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121008pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 564, "question": "Do you think that regardless of what happens in this case, would you like to see tougher gun control laws in America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RP", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 565, "answer": "It -- excuse me.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}]